<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lightGallery on</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/</link><description>Recent content in lightGallery on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 12:18:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Find JavaScript library usage</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/libstracker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/libstracker/</guid><description>Find JavaScript Library Usage libsTracker is a free and open-source tool that helps you find JavaScript library usage from the top million websites. JavaScript library usage from the top million websites Package Name Stars Number of websites vue 200717 37311 react 197763 190327 bootstrap 160399 182656 d3 103436 198622 axios 97318 49021 three.js 86874 3087 angular 84828 9093 ant-design 82655 774 material-ui 82632 659 font-awesome 70442 15895 svelte 63227 1601 reveal.</description></item><item><title>Download YouTube Thumbnails</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/download-youtube-thumbnails/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/download-youtube-thumbnails/</guid><description>Download YouTube Thumbnails Simply paste the URL of the YouTube video, and instantly download its thumbnail in various resolutions such as HD, SD, and more. Get Thumbnail Image HD Image (1280x720) Download SD Image (640x480) Download Normal Image (480x360) Download Normal Image (320x180) Download Normal Image (120x90) Download About YouTube Thumbnail Downloader For each YouTube video, YouTube generates multiple thumbnail sizes including HD Image (1280x720), SD Image (640x480), Normal Image (480x360), Small Image (320x180), and Extra Small Image (120x90).</description></item><item><title>jQuery to javascript converter</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/jquery-to-js-converter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/jquery-to-js-converter/</guid><description>jQuery to javascript converter Convert your jQuery scripts to efficient JavaScript directly in your browser. Receive reliable, chainable, modern JavaScript code instantly that can be used as a minimal utility library, while keeping your existing code untouched.
View on GitHub 100% Test Coverage Generated javascript for all methods except Enter jQuery code clear fullscreen exit Convert to JavaScript JavaScript Output Copy fullscreen exit Why?</description></item><item><title>Demos</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/demos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/demos/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>blog</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/license/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 12:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lightgalleryjs.com/license/</guid><description>Hobby $48 / lifetime For personal use. Purchase Now For one developer For one product Can't be used in a product for sale GitHub support only Lifetime free updates Team $118 / lifetime For small teams. Purchase Now For upto 8 developers For upto 5 products Can be used in a product for sale GitHub and email support Lifetime free updates Organization $188 / lifetime For large teams and organizations Purchase Now For unlimited developers For unlimited products Can be used in a product for sale GitHub, Email and Skype support Lifetime free updates Extended Commercial license If you want to include lightGallery as part of software developer kit (SDK), web application builder or website builder, downloadable or installable products like Wordpress themes, HTML templates,or something that produces copies that each use lightGallery, you need to choose the Extended Commercial license.</description></item></channel></rss>